Edvard Bech Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
Edvard Bech Collection
1830 - 1929 & 1972 - 2009
NPkMC-222-242
1 Linear Foot 275 items 2 boxes
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
Viggo Bech
This collection depicts the live of Edvard Bech, who born in Denmark in 1812 moved to New York in 1838 where he formed a trading firm that he would run for forty seven years. In 1863 he purchased a sixty-five acre farm along the Hudson River which he named “Rosenlund” and hired Danish architect Detlef Lineau to design the estate. This collection contains papers concerning the Bech famil history and businesses, materials compiled by Viggo Bech Rambusch for his monograph, and materials pretaining to the Roselunf estate.
Collection Overview
This collection contains letters, photos, documents, manuscripts, records and newspaper clippings concerning the Bech family history and businesses in the United States. It was compiled by Viggo Bech Rambusch through his creation of a monograph on the Bech family and life in Duchess County. This collection also contains material on Danish architect Lineau Detlef and his plans for the Rosenlund estate as well as a Daguerreotype of Edvard Bech’s estate.
Viggo Bech Rambusch donated his records concerning the history of Edvard Bech and Rosenlund to Marist College.
Historical Note
Edvard Bech was born May 4th, 1812 in Denmark. He was educated at the University of Copenhagen and his father Jorgen Bech was a prominent merchant. Bech emigrated to New York in 1838 where in 1842 he formed a trading firm which would run for forty seven years. After the death of his father Jorgen Peter Bech in 1848 he was left a large inheritance which he used to invest in the Tuckerman iron trade company which was then renamed Tuckerman and Bech. Bech became the Danish Consulate in New York from 1842 until 1858. He married Elizabeth Hossack in 1846 and moved to Poughkeepsie in 1851 where he lived for about ten years. During the Civil War Bech became very wealthy due to his business in the iron works.
In 1863 he purchased a sixty-five acre farm along the Hudson River which he named “Rosenlund” and hired Danish architect Detlef Lineau to design the estate. Construction was started and completed on a carriage house, a gate house, and a gardner’s cottage. Plans for a main house were created but not built due to Bech’s death in 1873. Lineau was commissioned to build the Bech Family Mausoleum in the Poughkeepsie cemetery for Edvard. His son, George Bech, continued to run Bech’s businesses until his own death in 1890. The order of the Marist Brother’s bought the estate in 1908. The three buildings designed by Lineau, now called Greystone, St. Peters and Kieran Gatehouse continue to be maintained by Marist College and gained historical recognition in 1991.
Restrictions to Access
There are no restrictions on this collection
Arrangement of the Collection
These records are organized into five series: 1) The Bech Family, has five subseries, 2) Edvard Bech, Ironmaster, has four subseries, 3) Danish Consul, has one subseries, 4) Rosenlund, has five subseries, 5) The Edvard Bech Monograph, has two subseries.
Series are arranged by subject, chronologically, or by type.
- 1. The Bech Family, 1830 - 2002; 1; Box: 1 Folders: 1 - 5
  Series contains portraits and pictures of the Bech family, history of the family, obituaries and death notices, materials about the familiy masoleum, and materials on the Linden Museum.
  Subject
  - Subseries 1.1: Portraits and Pictures of the Bech Family, 1.1; Box: 1 Folder: 1
    - Pictures of Edvard Bech’s grandfather, Jørgen Peter Bech (1743-1812) and Edvard Bech’s father, Jorgen Peter Bech (1782-1846). (Taped onto a sheet of paper), undated; Item 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Black and white portrait of Jorgen Peter Bech, undated; Item 2 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Pictures of Edvard Bech’s home in Denmark (taken from a painting), a Lego model of Edvard Bech’s home in Denmark, and a photograph of Edvard Bech’s home in Denmark. (Taped onto a sheet of paper), 1994; Item 3 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Three color photos of the exterior Edvard’s home in Denmark with the Black Rooster Symbol found on Jorgen Bech’s ships Photograph of the Black Rooster, the symbol on Jørgen Peter Bech’s ships., undated; Item 4 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Copy of a portrait of Edvard Bech., circa 1835; Item 5 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Black and white photo of Edvard Bech., undated; Item 6 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Sepia photo of Edvard Bech., undated; Item 7 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Photocopy enlargement of Edvard Bech photo., undated; Item 8 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Copy of a portrait of Elizabeth McCarty Hossack Bech, the wife of Edvard Bech., circa 1830; Item 9 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Portrait of Elizabeth Hossack Bech from the Royal Library in Copenhagen., undated; Item 10 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Copy of a family photograph., circa 1866; Item 11 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Photocopy of photo of Edvard Bech and Family found in Duchess County Historical Society Year Book, Volume 76., undated; Item 12 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Photocopy of photo of Mrs. Henri Braem., undated; Item 13 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Portrait of George Bech, Danish Consul., 1946; Item 14 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Picture of Carl Adolph Rothe Bech., undated; Item 15 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Folder of extra copies of Bech family home and negatives., undated; Item 16 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 1.2: Bech Family History, 1.2; Box: 1 Folder: 2
    - Letter to Viggo Rambusch from Edward Beck, describing his knowledge about Edvard Bech’s family including typed letter and handwritten timeline., January 30, 1990; Item 17 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Notes on Edvard Bech’s life with an attached letter to Viggo Rambusch from Edward J.A. Bech, sending these notes., January 30, 1990.; Item 18 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Information on Bech Family Service in the Danish Consulate., undated; Item 19 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Photocopied information on many Bech family members from Patriciske Slægter by Anden Samling., undated; Item 20 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Dutchess County Historical Society Year Book 1991- Volume 76, which includes the monograph on Edvard Bech entitled ‘Edvard Bech, Citizen of Poughkeepsie 1851-1873’ by Viggo Bech Rambusch with Walter Averill on pages 49-56. (Additional photocopies of the article are also included), Item 21 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Handwritten notes on Edvard Bech’s emigration and children by Viggo Rambusch., undated; Item 22 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Information on Edvard Bech as a student from the Copenhagen University Archives., undated; Item 23 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Handwritten information concerning Edvard Bech’s children by Viggo Rambusch., undated; Item 24 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Outline of Edvard Bech’s family, along with a family tree., undated; Item 25 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Copy of a Bech family tree., undated; Item 26 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Edvard Bech’s Family tree complied by Viggo Rambusch, 2008; Item 27 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Handwritten Notes on Elizabeth McCarty Hossack Bech and children by Viggo Rambusch., undated; Item 28 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Photocopy of article in Dutch entitled “Waldbygaard.”containing Bech family history, specifically Carl Bech., undated; Item 29 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Photocopy of a timeline of Edvard Bech’s life from the Henry Booth scrapbook., undated; Item 30 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Handwritten notes on Edvard Bech’s career in the Iron industry by Viggo Rambusch., undated; Item 31 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Hand drawn diagram of location of Bech’s companies in reference to the Hudson River., undated; Item 32 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Copy of Census from 1880 with Edvard Bech’s name listed, Item 33 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Copy of the New York Times announcement of George A. Bech’s marriage to Julia May entitled “Wedding in Baltimore.”, February 17, 1887; Item 34 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Letter to Eric Tillisch from Viggo B. Rambusch concerning Sophie Bech-Oxholm and the shooting competition she held each year., November 1, 1991; Item 35 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Copy of the minutes of the Meeting of the Board of Directors in Stockbridge, Massachusetts- with Elisabeth Bech’s signature., April 2, 1889; Item 36 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Notes on the Records of Christ Church 1911 about the specific Bech family monetary and volunteer contributions., Item 37 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Photocopy of “A Summary of the History of the Church of the Holy Comforter” in Poughkeepsie NY with highlighted information on Mr. and Mrs. Edward Bech and their specific contributions to the church., undated; Item 38 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Letter in Danish from August and Elisabeth Bech to Viggo B. Rambusch giving information on the Bech family., undated; Item 39 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 1.3: Obituaries and Death Notices, 1873 - 2002; 1.3; Box: 1 Folder: 3
    Chronological
    - Copies of Edvard Bech’s obituaries., 1873; Item 40 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Copy of the obituary of Edvard Bech from the “Berlingske Tidende.”, July 19, 1873; Item 41 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence between Mary Lou Davison and Viggo B. Rambusch concerning Edvard Bech’s obituary., April 1990; Item 42 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Letter to Viggo B. Rambusch from Mary Lou Davison concerning Edvard Bech’s obituary and a verbatim copy of Edvard Bechs obituary notice from the Poughkeepsie Daily Eagle, 1861., (1861) May 4, 1990; Item 43 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - “Death of Edward Bech of New York- 1873.”, Item 44 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Information about the death of Edvard Bech from the New York Times., July 12, 1873; Item 45 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Copy of the Final Accounting of the Executors of Edvard Bech., Item 46 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Copy of the obituary of George A. Bech from the Poughkeepsie Daily Eagle., April 18, 1890; Item 47 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Copy of the obituary of Elizabeth M. Bech from the Poughkeepsie Courier., June 1900; Item 48 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Letter to Viggo B. Rambusch from Eileen Hayden (Dutchess County Historical Society) with attached obituary of Mrs. Elizabeth M. Bech from the Poughkeepsie Courier (June 1900)., (June 1900) February 16, 1993; Item 49 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Copy of an article about the will of Elizabeth Bech from the Poughkeepsie Courier., June 1900; Item 50 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence between Viggo B. Rambusch and Dr. Ferdinand Opil concerning the obituary of Henri M. Braem (died in Vienna February 13, 1900) from 2002, translated from German to English. Attached is a copy of a German newspaper from February 14, 1900 with a translation of the death notice., (February 14, 1900) 2002; Item 51 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Copy of the article entitled “Kammerherreinde Oxholms Slægt,” both in Dutch and translated into English, about Sophie Oxholm’s death., undated; Item 52 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 1.4: Bech Family Mausoleum, 1.4; Box: 1 Folder: 4
    - Picture of the Bech Mausoleum in the Poughkeepsie Rural Cemetary in Poughkeepsie, New York, built in 1862. (attached to a piece of paper), undated; Item 53 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Color photo of the exterior of Bech vault and gate., undated; Item 54 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Color photo of the exterior side view of Bech vault., undated; Item 55 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Color photo of the exterior side view of Bech vault., undated; Item 56 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Color photo of the roof of the Bech vault., undated; Item 57 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Color photo of small roof window of Bech vault., undated; Item 58 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Color photo of the closed door to Bech vault., undated; Item 59 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Color photo of the open door to Bech vault., undated; Item 60 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Color photo of a key in the grass., undated; Item 61 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Color photo of the grave of Caroline Vassar Babcock., undated; Item 62 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Color photo of the interior of the Bech vault and coffins., undated; Item 63 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Color photo of a stained glass window., undated; Item 64 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Color photo of the resting place of Gorge Albert Bech., undated; Item 65 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Color photo of the tomb of Charlotte Elisabeth McCarty Bech., undated; Item 66 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Color photo of the tomb of Edward Bech., undated; Item 67 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Color photo of a mosaic cross., undated; Item 68 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Folder of duplicate photos and negatives., undated; Item 69 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Note from the Poughkeepsie Rural Cemetery with the superintendent Charles Fells phone number as well as Walter Averill’s contact information., undated; Item 70 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Information on the Bech family members interred in the Bech Mausoleum., undated; Item 71 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Copy of a letter to the superintendent of the Poughkeepsie Rural Cemetery from Sophie Oxholm (written May 4, 1929) concerning the poor condition of the Bech mausoleum., Item 72 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Copy of a letter to the superintendent of the Poughkeepsie Rural Cemetery from Sophie Oxholm (written July 18, 1929) concerning the cemetery and the family vault., Item 73 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Copy of a Surrogate’s Court Document - December 4th, 1972., December 4, 1972; Item 74 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Letter to Catha Rambusch from Vicki Fells concerning a toll call to the cemetery - December 13th, 1990., December 13, 1990; Item 75 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 1.5: The Linden Museum, 1.5; Box: 1 Folder: 5
    - Copies of a Dutch article from the Berlignske Tidende, with an English translation, about the Linden Museum and the Bech family., January 26, 1910; Item 76 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Letter to Dietrich Neumann from Viggo B. Rambusch asking for information on the Linden Museum., December 27, 2004; Item 77 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Letter to Viggo B. Rambusch from Dietrich Neumann concerning the Linden Museum in Stuttgart., January 11, 2005; Item 78 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Information on the Linden Museum from internet sources., undated; Item 79 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 2. Edvard Bech, Ironmaster, 2; Box: 1 Folders: 6 - 9
  Series contains materials pretaining to the painting of the ironworks, history and information on the iron industry, Forest of the Dean Iron ore company records, and information on the New York Canals.
  - Painting of the ironworks, 2.1; Box: 1 Folder: 6
    - Letter to Viggo B. Rambusch from Edward J.A. Bech acknowledging the article Rambusch sent him and offering to send a copy of a painting of the iron mines., September 7, 1989; Item 80 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Letter to Viggo B. Rambusch from Edward J.A. Bech sending a photograph of a painting of the iron mines by E. Riehardt -attached to a copy of a letter to Edward J.A. Bech from Viggo B. Rambusch thanking him for a photo of an oil painting of the iron mines and asking for any additional information., November 2, 1989-January 30, 1990; Item 81 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Notes on the painting “Bech’s Furnace- 1850,” now in the Yale Museum., undated; Item 82 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Copies of correspondence concerning the painting “Poughkeepsie Iron Works (Bech’s Furnace).”, undated; Item 83 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Color copy of the painting “Poughkeepsie Iron Works (Bech’s Furnace)” by Carmiencke., undated; Item 84 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Black and White Copy of the painting “Factory on the Hudson” by Carmiencke., undated; Item 85 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Bill to Viggo B. Rambusch from the Yale University Art Gallery for a photograph of the painting “Factory on the Hudson” by Carmiencke., May 18, 1990; Item 86 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Drawing of “Poughkeepsie and its Foundries at Night” from “Picturesque America.”, undated; Item 87 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Notes on the painting “Hudson River at Poughkeepsie.”, undated; Item 88 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Copy of the painting “Hudson River at Poughkeepsie” showing the ironworks., undated; Item 89 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Copy of an unlabeled picture., undated; Item 90 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Copy of a picture of the Ericsson Statue in Battery Park., undated; Item 91 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Copy of an engraving of the Delamater Iron Works., undated; Item 92 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Copy of a letter to William Cuffe from Viggo B. Rambusch asking for a smaller copy of the Bech Iron Works painting., May 31, 1990; Item 93 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Copy of a letter to Ella Stedner from Viggo B. Rambusch sending twenty dollars for the catalog on Albert Insley., August 19, 1991; Item 94 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Index of paintings by Albert Insley, ‘The Hudson from the Palisades’ highlighted., undated; Item 95 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Copy of a letter to Roy Blankenship from Viggo B. Rambusch giving information about a painting of the iron works by Albert Insley., October 30, 1991; Item 96 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Copy of a letter to Roy Blankenship from Viggo B. Rambusch sending a photograph., January 10, 1992; Item 97 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Copy of the painting “Hudson River at Poughkeepsie” showing the ironworks., undated; Item 98 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - “The Delicate Palette of Albert Insley 1842-1937.”, undated; Item 99 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Dutchess County Historical Society Year Book 1982 Volume 67, an article on the paintings of the Poughkeepsie Iron Works., undated; Item 100 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Copy of a letter to William P. McDermott from Viggo B. Rambusch asking for the contact information of Jeffrey A. Arons., January 30, 1990; Item 101 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Copy of correspondence between Viggo B. Rambusch and Mary Lou Davison concerning an address for Jeffrey A. Arons and other information on Edvard Bech., March 1990; Item 102 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - History and Information on the Iron Industry, 1901 - 1994; 2.2; Box: 1 Folder: 7
    - Information on the Forest of Dean., undated; Item 103 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - “A Report of the Mohawk-Hudson Area Survey” edited by Robert M. Vogel., undated; Item 104 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Copy of the article “The Iron Heart of the Hudson Valley.”, undated; Item 105 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Copy of the article “Ornamental Iron” by Patricia Edwards Clyne., undated; Item 106 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Pages from “New York- A Guide to the Empire State.”, undated; Item 107 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Information on the Poughkeepsie Iron Company from “History of Dutchess County New York” by James H. Smith., undated; Item 108 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Information about Edvard Bech’s iron mines from “The Eagle’s History of Poughkeepsie from the Earliest Settlements -1683-1905” by Edmund Platt., undated; Item 109 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Viggo B. Rambusch’s notes on the Poughkeepsie Iron Company., undated; Item 110 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - The Dutchess Historian- information on addition of the Edmund Platt Diaries to the Dutchess County Historical Society Library., Winter 1993; Item 111 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Information about the Port Henry Iron Ore Company., undated; Item 112 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Information on the iron mine of Port Henry., undated; Item 113 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Copy of a letter to Professor Thomas Casey from Viggo B. Rambusch sending him a copy of an article about Edvard Bech’s iron works., January 30, 1990; Item 114 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Letter to Viggo B. Rambusch from Noel Zimmerman concerning additional information about Edvard Bech and his iron mines., July 30, 1990; Item 115 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Letter to Viggo B. Rambusch from Noel Zimmerman giving the name of the Port Henry historian with an attached copy of a letter to Eleanore Hall from Viggo B. Rambusch asking for information about Edvard Bech and the Port Henry Iron Ore Mine., September 5, 1990- - September 13, 1990; Item 116 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Copy of a letter to Eleanore Hall (Sherman Library) from Viggo B. Rambusch asking for any information on Edvard Bech and the Port Henry Iron Mine., February 27, 1991; Item 117 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Copy of correspondence between Viggo B. Rambusch and Jacqueline A. Viestenz of the Sherman Free Library concerning information about the Port Henry Iron Mine., undated; Item 118 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Copy of a letter to the Adirondack Museum from Viggo B. Rambusch asking for information about Edvard Bech and the Bayfront Mine., February 27, 1991; Item 119 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Letter to Viggo B. Rambusch from Walter Averill giving a list of iron mines in Dutchess County from 1869., June 17, 1991; Item 120 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - List of iron mines and their locations., undated; Item 121 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Letter to Viggo B. Rambusch from Walter Averill sending an article about the Tilly Foster mines., October 25, 1991; Item 122 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Copy of an article on the Tilly Foster Iron Mine., undated; Item 123 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Copy of a letter to Sally Syphers from Viggo B. Rambusch asking for information about the iron industry in Dutchess County., June 7, 1993; Item 124 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Letter to Viggo B. Rambusch from Hallie E. Bond of the Adirondack Museum, with the information her librarian found on Edvard Bech and the iron industry attached., July 23, 1993; Item 125 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Letter to John Miller from Viggo B. Rambusch asking for information about the iron works; attached is a faxed message giving names and phone numbers of other people to ask., April 14, 1994; Item 126 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - “The 150th Anniversary D&H Map” by the Bridge Line Historical Society, giving information on railways., undated; Item 127 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - History of the Bech and Fallkill Iron works, researched and written by Viggo B. Rambusch., undated; Item 128 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Indentures tracking the ownership of former Bech property., 1901-1973; Item 129 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Forest of Dean Iron ore company records, 1888 - 1902; 2.3; Box: 1 Folder: 8
    - Copies of Records for the Forest of Dean Iron Ore Company., undated; Item 130 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Copy of letter to Jorgen Bech from Henri Braem concerning the name change of the iron mine., June 29, 1888; Item 131 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Copy of Forest of Dean Iron Ore Company Balance Sheets., 1889; Item 132 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Copy of Forest of Dean Iron Ore Company Balance Sheets., 1890; Item 133 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Copy of Forest of Dean Iron Ore Company Balance Sheets., 1891; Item 134 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Copy of Forest of Dean Iron Ore Company Balance Sheets., 1893; Item 135 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Copy of letter to Jorgen Bech from Henri Braem informing him of his dividends., February 3, 1893; Item 136 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Copy of Forest of Dean Iron Ore Company Balance Sheets., 1894; Item 137 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Copy of the Records of the Amount of Ore Mined and Carted to the River., 1894; Item 138 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Copy of Forest of Dean Iron Ore Company Balance Sheets., 1895; Item 139 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Copy of Forest of Dean Iron Ore Company Balance Sheets., 1896; Item 140 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Copy of Forest of Dean Iron Ore Company Balance Sheets., 1897; Item 141 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Copy of Forest of Dean Iron Ore Company Balance Sheets., 1898; Item 142 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Copy of Forest of Dean Iron Ore Company Balance Sheets., 1899; Item 143 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Copy of Forest of Dean Iron Ore Company Balance Sheets., 1900; Item 144 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Copy of Forest of Dean Iron Ore Company Balance Sheets., 1901; Item 145 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Copy of Forest of Dean Iron Ore Company Balance Sheets., 1902; Item 146 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Copy of Forest of Dean Iron Ore Company Balance Sheets., 1903; Item 147 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Copy of Forest of Dean Iron Ore Company Balance Sheets., 1904; Item 148 (Box 1, Folder 8)